A Guide to the VCU Libraries Zine collection, 1979-2017
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Once Upon A Time... A Person Picked This Up...(What Next?), undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
- One Dimensional Life in the Three Dimensional World, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
- One Thousand Feathers The Two aka Recession Proof 1, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
- One Thousand Feathers the Three aka The Primordial Traditionalist II, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
- One Thousand Feathers The Four aka J. J. Krupert I, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
- ONT Road, no. 14, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Open Book A 24-Hour Zine, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Open Minds, no. 1-3, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Open Minds, no. 1-3, 2012 - 2013 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Open Minds, no. 7, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Oregon Hill Cats, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
- over the government by force, vol. 1, no.1, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Opencrotch, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Passenger Side, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Patch, no. 5, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Patrica Letters, The, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Peace You'd Die For, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Pearl Tongue, no. 4, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Persistence Bmx Journal, no. 5, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Peop(le)s, no. 5, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Revenant, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Pigeon House, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Pigeon-Man, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Pilcrow, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Pimp, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Pinellas Zine Scene, no. 1-2, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Pit, no. 4, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
- pleiades, the, no. 12-13, 16, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Poems to Crush Your Soul, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Poems: People Making Stupid Shapes with Words, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Poets Against the War, no. 3, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Poets Espresso, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Poopy Times, The, vol. 1, no. 4, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Popular Metaphorics, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Postal Curiosities & Delights, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Preparation X, no. 7, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Pretty Pussy! Hair Care for Sensitive Girls, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Primordial Traditionalist, The, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Pulp Radio, vol. 2, no. 5, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Pumpkin, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Prozac & Corn Flakes, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Queer Ramblings, no. 36, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- R.I.P. Geegar No Hard Feelings, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Rabid Bager, no. 1, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Rabid Bager, no. 2, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Rad Dad, no. 13, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
- a pathetically incomplete list of radical books for kids (and adults), undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Rare Copy, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Re: my snow-job, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- recluse zine, no. 3, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Red Pen, no. 2, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- refreshing times flow gently, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- the remainders, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
- rendezvous with violence, no. 6, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Resonance Evil w/CD, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Retell Your Rumors, no. 2, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Rex and the Knight, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- richmond poets against the war!, vol. 1, no. 1, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Richmond Reproductive Freedom Project!, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Richmond Reproductive Freedom Project 3 copies, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Richmond Reproductive Freedom Project Ver. 3, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Riger Mortis, vol. 1, no. 2, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Riot Librarrrian, no. 1, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Robot Boy, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Robot Investigator, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Rocks Off, no. 1, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Rocks off, no. 5, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- A Rough Guide to Bicycle Maintenance, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- rrrl girlz, vol. 2, no. 1, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Rubber on Central Ave., 2010 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Sabulous, no. 2, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Sassy Junior, no. 1, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Sassy Junior, no. 2, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Sassy Junior Magazine, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Scam, no. 4, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Screamqueen Distro Summer 2002 Catalog (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Secret Identity, no.1, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Secret Identity Two, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Secret Prison, no. 2, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Self-Defense, no. 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Sewing and Drawing, no. 1, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Sewing and Drawing, no. 2, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Sex, Celebration, Justice: A Keynote for QD2002, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Sex Face, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Shapes, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
- She Opens Her Eyes, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Soplifting: the art and science, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Sidenotes, no. 5, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
- The Silk City Series, vol. 1 Story 1, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- The Silk City Series, vol. 1 Story 2, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- The Silk City Series, vol. 1 Story 3, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- A Silk City Series Supplement: 7 Objects from a Box in the Attic, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Complete Silk City Series, The, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Sincerely Amendment, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Six Letters, no. 1, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Sketch Dump Chronicles vol. 1, animal sketches, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Skinny, no. 1-19, 23, 25-26, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Slow Death, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Slant, no. 1-10, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Sleep Related, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Slug and Lettuce, no. 69, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Slug and Lettuce, no. 72, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Slug and Lettuce, no. 75, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Slug and Lettuce, no. 82, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Slug and Lettuce, no. 84, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Slug and Lettuce, no. 86, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Slug and Lettuce, no. 87, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Slug and Lettuce, no. 88, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Small Drawings, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Smash the Pastryarchy, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- smith mini comic, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Smut Ball, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
- smut peddler: an anthology of erotic comics, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Smyle vol III, no. 3, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. [bomb], 1995 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 00, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. #, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 5, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 6, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 7, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- so what?, no. 8, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
- so what?, no. 9-14, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 9, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 10 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 11, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 12, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 13, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 14, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 15, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 16, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 20, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
- so what?, vol. 1, no. 23, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
- so what?, vol. 1, The Best of the 1st regular editions, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Soap Box Mess Up, no. 3, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Social Suicide Issue, no. 1, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
- someone loves me in ohio, no. 5, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Sometimes I Have to Go Around Will's Curb, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Sound Bill, vol. 1, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Sore, no. 14, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Some True Stories, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Spare Parts, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- the spazz report, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Splotch!, vol. 1, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Sqeek, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Stacks, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Star Gang, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Strange Deceive Stories, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Stash, no. 2-3, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Steakhouse, no. 1, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Sticks, vol 1., no. 2, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Strange Voyage of the Leona Joyce, The, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Strike, no. 1-2, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Still Life, no. 2, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Stress Anger Depression Anxiety: a coping skills zine, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Sty-Zine, no. 26, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- suburban sanity no. 6: because I found no substitute for sense, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Super Tiny Lucky Cat Zine, no. 1, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Support (support information for the sexually abused), 2002 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Shuke, The: Support Your Local Everything, no. 1, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Supporting Prisoners and Acting fro Radical Change, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Syndicate Product no 17 / Sybdicate Consumpation 2010, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Systris does the Podosphere, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Systris Reader, The, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Tail of the Samurai Cat, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Take the Toys Away from the Boys, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Taken for a Ride: my night in the cash cab, 2012 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Tales from the Natural World, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Talk to the Scarf 'cos yhe face ain't listening, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Taller Than the World, no. 3 / Lift no. 0, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Targential Ferver, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Tartar and Gravities, no. 1, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Tazewell's Favorite Eccentric, no. 4, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Teenage death songs, no. 10, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Tell the Boss, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Tell the Boss, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Temperature Wise, no. 1, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Temperature Wise, no. 2, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Tenacious: writings from women in prison, no. 1, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Then Make Your Own Comic, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
- there an artist (ecco un artista), vol. 1, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
- These are the Days, no. 2-4, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
- This, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- This, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- This Could Be You But It's Not, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
- This Horror Most Unreal, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Three Entire Minutes, no. 5, undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Time Blur, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Times Graffix, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Time Shifting, no.. 1-2, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Today Terrific, no. 6-8, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Torture, no. 1, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Turtle Press Magazine, no. 2, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Trailer Trash, no. 7, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Trash, no. 25, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Try to wake up with a smile on your face!, no. 1, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- twigmama, no. 5, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Untitled Flipbook, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Untitled, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Untitled, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Untitled [Blackberry], undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Untitled [photography album], undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Untitled [Sam Hildergartner], 2010 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Untitled [photo album by emily marie jones], undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Untitled [drawings by Candice Corbin], 2010 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- bunnies on ice, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- untitled, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
- untitled, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
- untitled (Box 21, Folder 8)
- untitled [and sometimes people are just hiding from the weather], undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
- untitled [Daniel Stettner], undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Untitled [Sam Hildergartner], 2010 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Untitled [zine resource guide], 2003 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Untitled [ Molly Bersin], 2011 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Ugly, The Review, The, no. 1, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Ugly, The Review, The, no. 2, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Ultimate Fight Comic, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Underwraps, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Unicorn Poop, no. 5-6, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Untitled [photos], undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Untitled [refrigerator magnet zine], undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
- urinal fanzine, the, no. 5, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Urine Trouble, vol. 2, no. 4, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Veer, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Vinyl Vagabonds, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Virginia Workers' Rights, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Vitaphobia, no. 8, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Vulva-can-0, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Waiting, no. 5, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Wall, The, no. 1, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Wall Street Cat: Money Takes Naps, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Warship Say "10", no. 1, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Warship Say "10", no. 2, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Warship Say "10", no. 3-5, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
- We Don't Talk About Love, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- We're Doing Something, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Welcome to Bend, no. 1, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Welcome to the Neighborhood, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- What Does It Mean To Live?, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- White Elephants, no. 3, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Whizzbanger Guide to Zine Distributions The, no. 2, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Why the Exhibit Was Canceled, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
- William's Horra Short Stories, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Wingnut Anarchist Archive, The, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
- With Heart in Mouth, no. 1-2, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Wizards don't know math, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
- wolf tickets, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Women's studies @ VCU, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Woolgatherer, no. 1, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Word Salad, no. 1, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Words I Just Couldn't Use: Help Yourself to Each Word Different, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Worrisome and Bothersome Questions, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Worst Future Ever, no. 2, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Writer's Playground, vol. 1, no.1, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Writing Down, Speaking Up: Words of Today's Feminists, no. 2, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Young Democratic Socialists of America at VCU, no. 1, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
- you've got a friend in pennsylvania, no. 3, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Your Pretty Face is Going Straight to Hell!, no. 8, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Zine Crush: Confessions of Like, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Yawabango, no. 1, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- The Yellow Journal, vol. X, no. 6, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- You Are Not Alone in Feeling Alone, no. 3-4, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
- You Cannot Duplicate Me, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- you forget (her), 2007 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- You Gotta Have It!, no. 1, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
- How is A..., undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Zapruder, who made dresses, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Zen of Henry, The, no. 2, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
- a zine about women's self defense, no. 1, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Zineguide: The Ultimate Independent Press Resource Guide, no. 5, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Zine Night Zine, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Zinetopia, no. 0-2, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Zine World, no. 30-31, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 39)